<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document>

    <properties>
        <title>NeuClear - Commons</title>
        <author email="pelle@neubia.com">Pelle Braendgaard</author>
    </properties>

    <body>
        <section name="Introduction">
            <p>
				This is a collection of common tools and utilities used throughout the
                NeuClear framework. They concern them selves mainly with Crypto, but also all the little generalistic
                bits and pieces that dont quite fit neatly elsewhere. It is not really intended as a
                library for use outside the NeuClear framework, as such it is currently not well documented.
            </p>
            <p>
                Much of the crypto code provide some useful abstractions ontop of the often complex JCE architecture from Sun.
                If there is interest we will probably repackage it in the next version as neuclear-crypto and document it better.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section name="[28 April, 2004] New release 0.7">
            <p>
                Panama City, 28 April, 2004. We are happy to announce
                the 0.7 release of NeuClear Commons.
            </p>
            <p>
                Main goal of this release is to support the
                <a href="http://dev.neuclear.org/id/">0.9 release
                of NeuClear ID</a>.
                <a href="http://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=90470">Download it today and join in the NeuClear revolution</a>.
                Major new features are:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>New Swing based Passphrase Agent</li>
                <li>DefaultSigner is now completely interactive.</li>
                <li>SQLSigner stores Public Private Key Pairs in SQL using Hibernate.</li>
                <li>Removed all old SQL support code.</li>
                <li>Added in memory caching to Public Key Resolver</li>
                <li>Added new interactive signing model with the BrowsableSigner interface</li>
                <li>New SetPublicKeyCallback method for returning the public key in interactive applications</li>
            </ul>

        </section>
        <section name="[23 March, 2004] New release 0.6">
            <p>
                Panama City, 23rd of March, 2004. We are happy to announce
                the 0.6 release of NeuClear Commons.
            </p>
            <p>
                Main goal of this release is to support the coming
                <a href="http://old.neuclear.org/id/">0.9 release
                of NeuClear ID</a>.
                <a href="http://sourceforge.net/project/showfiles.php?group_id=90470">Download it today and join in the NeuClear revolution</a>.
            </p>

        </section>
    </body>

</document>
